module.exports = [
  { question: "What is the name of Bastion's Bird?", answer: "Ganymede" },
  { question: "How many Blinks can Tracer have stored at once?",  answer: "3" },
  { question: "What is Mercy's full name?", answer: "Angela Ziegler" },
  { question: "Which Character made it into the game solely based on the art design?", answer: "Reaper" },
  { question: "How old is D.Va?", answer: "19" },
  { question: "What was Overwatch originally titled?", answer: "Titan" },
  { question: "How old is Reinhardt?", answer: "61" },
  { question: "What is Junkrat's full name?" answer: "Jamison Fawkes" },
  { question: "What clan are Hanzo and Genji from?", answer: "Shimada Clan" },
  { question: "How much damage does Winston's Jump Jet do?", answer: "25" },
  { question: "How many playable characters are in Overwatch?", answer: "24" },
  { question: "How much damage does Widowmaker do fully charged?", answer: "300" },
  { question: "What is the name of the comic that features Roadhog and Junkrat together?", answer: "Going Legit" },
  { question: "How many buttons in the main menu of Overwatch?", answer: "8" },
  { question: "What is Tracer wearing on her chest?", answer: "Chronal Accelerator" },
  { question: "Genji can reflect Soldier: 76's healing ability (true/false)", answer: "true" },
  { question: "Which map has Winston's armor hanging from the ceiling?", answer: "Watchpoint Gibraltar" },
  { question: "What is D.Va's mech's clip size?", answer: "infinite" },
  { question: "What country is Junkrat from?", answer: "Australia" },
  { question: "Genji can reflect Zarya's Ult, Graviton Surge (true/false)", answer: "true" },
  { question: "What is Tracer's full name?", answer: "Lena Oxton" },
  { question: "D.Va is streaming whenever she is in a battle (true/false)", answer: "true" },
  { question: "What is Reaper's total clip size?", answer: "8" },
  { question: "Competitive Mode seasons are how long? (in months)" answer: "3" }
]
